<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Side By Side</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="Photo">Photo</string>
    <string name="Folder">Folder</string>
    <string name="noBluetooth">Bluetooth is no available on this phone.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="photoCountNote">This tells you how many photos you have taken on a day. It will increment by 1  every time you take a photo using the in-app camera or if you take using the phone\'s camera and import the photo into the app\'s folder.</string>
    <string name="folderNote">This folder button opens up an folder. You can import from the main album where every photo is displayed. Once imported, the photo will show in the layout. You can also choose two photos to compare.</string>
    <string name="settingNote">The setting lets you set a time in the day at which a notification will pop up, reminding you to take a photo.</string>
    <string name="cameraNote">Whatever photo you take with this in-app camera will automatically saved to the app\'s folder. Also taking one photo will increment the daily photo count by 1.</string>
    <string name="editNote">With Edit, can you input the weight and other health info for one particular photo. You can also write a few sentences for comment on how you did. Those numerical info will be used when two photos are compared. The ENABLE TOUCH button is there because when you want to pinch/zoom you have to press it. The maker of this app wasn\'t able to properly fit a photo into the screen when the pinch/zoom enabled by default. Sorry.</string>
    <string name="compareNote">There is horizontal/vertical mode for comparing landscape/portrait photos. To select a photo to display, you can click the photo frame when the TOUCH is DISABLED or in the menu always. After you have selected two photos, you can share or save the collage.</string>
    <string name="file">/DCIM/raspberry</string>
</resources>
